美…好…的…早晨到了
Morning's here
早晨又来到
The morning's here
阳光露脸
Sunshine is here
晴空万里
The sky is clear
美好的早晨又来到
The morning's here
你一定要唱吗  今天是星期六
Do you have to do that? It's Saturday!
别这样嘛
Oh, come on!
早晨来到了
Morning's here!
Morning's here
早晨又来到
The morning's here
阳光露脸…
Sunshine is here
我讨厌这间公寓
I hate this apartment!
我讨厌墙壁的颜色  我讨厌这里还有鸟禽的味道
I hate the color of these walls! I hate that this place still smells like bird!
我讨厌那个唱歌的人
I hate that singing guy!
不会吧  我好喜欢他
Are you kidding? I love that guy!
美好的早晨又来到…
Morning's here, morning is...
闭嘴
Stop it!
小心我宰了你
I will kill you.
我讨厌我的房间那么小
I hate that my room is so small.
空间够用就好  学学我吧
I have all the space I need. Just do what I did.
莫妮卡  你连床都没有  就是睡在地上的懒骨头
Monica, you don't even have a bed. You sleep in a ball on the floor!
你知道什么  我真的受不了你的抱怨
You know what? I am tired of your bellyaching.
我很努力想把这里布置得舒适些
I've worked really hard at making this a nice place for us to live.
我知道  对不起
I know. I'm so sorry.
对不起  没关系
I'm sorry, okay?
看  这房子多好啊
See, This is a great apartment.
闭嘴   这里简直烂死了
Shut up. This place is a hole.
老友记  第四季  第19集  忙中出错
Friends  S04E19  The One With All The Haste
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
哎呀  我还是不敢相信你居然戴了耳环
Oh, blimey, I still can't believe you've got an earring!
我知道  我知道  我是谁  大卫鲍伊
I know, I know. Who am I? David Bowie?
他也会戴耳环吗
He does that?
不知道   管他呢
I don't know. Whatever. Ha, ha.
我觉得你这样看起来像个危险人物
Well, I think it makes you look really dangerous.
我知道
Oh, I know. Ha-ha-ha.
你知道什么啊
You know what?
要不是你  我永远不会戴耳环
I never would've gotten this if it weren't for you.
真的  跟你在一起时  我就像
No, really. When I'm with you, I'm like...
变了一个人  我爱那个家伙
...this whole other guy. I love that guy!
我是指  我更爱你一点
I mean, I love you too. A lot.
不过那家伙
But that guy!
我爱那个家伙
I love that guy!
我爱你们两个
I love both of you. Ah, heh.
真希望我不用走就好了
I wish I didn't have to go.
那就别走
Then don't.
留下来  别急着回伦敦
Stay here. Just don't go so soon to London,
再多呆一天  罗斯
Just one more day. Oh, Ross.
就多一天  求你别再引诱我了
One more day. Please don't do this to me again.
我也想啊  但我耽误了好多工作  会被开除的
You know I'd stay, but I've already missed so much work. They'll fire me.
那样  你就可以想待多久就待多久了
So? Then you could stay as long as you want.
真是那样就好了
I wish I could.
不  不要  不要收拾啊
Oh, no, don't... Don't... Don't start packing.
拜托啦
Come on.
我不是现在就走
I don't think you understand packing.
我只是不想临走时再收拾
I don't want to leave it till the last minute.
上次走的太匆忙   结果把我的短裤忘在这里了
Last time I packed in a rush, I left my knickers here.
我知道  我试着偷穿了一下
Yeah, I know. I, uh, tried them on.
不会吧
You didn't!
不  逗你玩的  我可不想成为 "那家伙"
No, I didn't. I didn't want to be "that guy."
哈罗
Hello.
呵  呵  呵
Ho, ho, ho.
什么   你的裤子
Excuse me? Your pants.
喔对  你喜欢吗
Oh, yeah! You like them?
我只是去了二手店买了一大堆孕妇装
I went to a used clothes store and got a bunch of maternity stuff.
这些裤子好舒服
These are so comfortable.
菲比  那些是圣诞裤
Uh, Pheebs, those are, uh, Santa pants.
什么   圣诞裤
What? Santa pants.
圣诞老人的裤子
Santa Claus' pants.
才不是呢   这是孕妇裤
Nuh-uh. They're maternity pants.
你看  还附赠宝宝姓名表
They even came with a list of baby names. See?
这些是好名字  这些是坏名字
These names are good, and these are bad.
嘿   嘿
Hey! Hey.
嘿  菲比
Hey, Pheebs.
那个  驯鹿都好吗
So, how are the elves?
我不知道   那你  那个
I don't know. How are the, uh, you know?
你的衣服看着好好笑啊
Your clothes aren't funny.
嘿  小子  我该穿什么去看 "尼克队"比赛
Hey, guys, what should I wear to a Knicks game?
上面印有  "我不属于这里" 的衣服
Uh, a T-shirt that says, "I Don't Belong Here"?
你们有票
You have tickets?
我妈离婚时分到我爸赛季的票   就送给我了
Yeah, my mom got my dad's season tickets in the divorce, so she gave them to me.
很显然  座位相当的好
Apparently, they're good seats.
天哪  几乎就在球场边上
Oh, my God! Those are almost on the floor!
你们想要吗
Do you guys want these?
废话  想  当然想
Yeah! Yeah, we do!
好吧  给你们
Well, you got them!
太好了  只要把公寓这里还给我们就行了
All right! Just give us our apartment back.
想不到有这一招
Whoa, I didn't see that coming.
你是说真的
Are you serious?
拜托  我们知道这票值多少
Come on. We know what these are worth.
你们以为我们是白痴吗
Do you think we're stupid?
不是白痴  你们比我们想像的要狡猾多了
Not stupid. You're meaner than I thought.
怎么样  想都别想
What do you say? Forget it.
我才不会为了几张篮球票  放弃我的单身公寓
Okay? I'm not giving up my bachelor pad for some basketball seats!
你的 "单身公寓"
Your "bachelor pad"?
你有女孩住过这吗
Have you even had a girl here?
没有
No.
但是乔伊有过  我早上都会跟她们聊天
But Joey has, and I usually talk to them in the morning time.
是的  没错
Yeah, you do.
（中央咖徘厅）
拜托啦
Come on!
阿甘  请给我两杯奇诺
Yes,Gunther, can I get two cups of chino, please?
点的不错
Good one.
拜托  季票
Come on. Season tickets.
季票  你知道那代表什么
Season tickets! You know what that means?
别想了  我绝不让出公寓
Forget it. I'm not giving up the apartment.
小时候  我爸的公司都会送季票
Oh come—look,When I was a kid, my dad's company gave season tickets...
给业绩第一的业务员  我爸从来没拿到过
...to the Number 1 salesman every year. All right? My dad never won.
不过  他也不在业务部  但我还是一直耿耿于怀
Of course, he wasn't in sales. But still, I never ever, ever forgot that!
你们在啊  嘿
Hey guys! Hey.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我们开你的玩笑还不够吗
We don't make enough fun of you already?
艾蜜莉说服我去穿的
Oh, yeah. Emily convinced me to do it.
你知道《轰》合唱团解散了吧
You do know that Wham broke up?
我喜欢  艾蜜莉也喜欢  这点最重要
I like it. And Emily likes it. And that's what counts.
你们怎么样
So, uh, how are you guys doing?
不要觉得戴了耳环还能算正常
Don't try and talk all normal with that thing in your ear.
艾蜜莉呢
Where's Emily?
去跟她舅舅道别去了
Ugh, she's saying goodbye to her uncle.
她不喜欢住这吗  对  对啊
Didn't she, like, just get here? Yeah! Yeah.
别激动  大哥
Easy, tiger.
我真的很讨厌这样
I just hate this so much.
每次去机场接她  我都好开心
Every time I go pick her up at the airport, it's so great.
但是我又会想  "过两天又要送她来机场了"
But I'm thinking, "I'll be right back in a couple of days, dropping her off."
那你要怎么办  也没办法
So, what'll you do? There's nothing to do.
她住那  我住这
She lives there. I live here.
她得搬来这里
She'd have to move here.
她应该搬来这里
She should move here.
什么
What?
我可以叫她跟我住  你说真的吗
I can ask her to live with me. Are you serious?
为什么不  我说  为什么不  你们才认识六个星期
Why not? I mean, why not? You've only known her six weeks!
我冰箱里有盒牛奶放得比你们这个还更久
I've got a carton of milk in my fridge I've had a longer relationship with.
听着  我跟她在一起时  就像
Look, guys, when I'm with her, it's like...
她会激发出我最好的一面
Uh, she brings out this great side of me.
我的意思是  我爱她  你知道吗
I mean, I love her, you know?
我也爱那盒牛奶
And I love the milk!
但我不会让某个英国女生搬来和我住
But I won't ask some British girl to move in with me.
乔伊  现在该你说了
Joey, you say things now.
罗斯  他说得对  艾蜜莉很棒
Look, Ross. He's right. Emily's great.
她很棒
She's great!
但这样太快了  你只会吓到她
But this is too soon. You're only gonna scare her.
我不想吓到她  没错
I don't wanna do that. No.
你不想搞砸了  就别太心急
You don't want to wreck it. Don't go too fast.
你们说得对  我知道  你们是对的
No. You're right. I know, you're right.
我不会这样做的
I'm not going to do it.
谢了  两位  不客气
Thanks guys. No problem.
记得要走时摇它两下 （《轰》所唱的歌词）
Just remember to wake us up before you go-go.
太难了  太难了
It's too hard. Too hard!
好了  两位  最后的机会
All right, boys. Last chance for the tickets.
否则  我就送给我的新男友  约书亚
Otherwise, I give them to my new boyfriend, Joshua.
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
等一下  拜托  跟她们换啦
Wait, wait. Come on, come on! Let's trade.
时机正好  我刚把马桶给堵住了
The timing's perfect! I just clogged the toilet!
我跟你一样想要球票  但住过这里
Look, I want those basketball seats as much as you do! Okay, but we can't leave in the small apartment...
就觉得对面太小了  你看过 "献给阿尔吉侬的花束"吗
...after we've lived here! Ever read Flowers for Algernon?
有
Yes.
你看过 "运动画报" 吗
Ever read Sports Illustrated?
没有  我没偷看过你的
No, I didn't read yours!
我们今晚就可以去看球
We can go to the game tonight!
她们提出比季票更好的东西
The only way I'll consider this...
我才要考虑
...is if they offer more than just season seats.
是 "尼克队"  去他的 "尼克队"
It's the Knicks! Screw the Knicks.
我不是那个意思  我是说
I didn't mean that. I just meant...
这层公寓的价值要更大
...that the apartment is worth so much more.
"尼克队"万岁
And the Knicks rule all.
对  "尼克队"万岁
Yeah, the Knicks rule all!
嘿  怎么样  要不要
Hey, so? Are you going to do it?
不要  因为这个交易不公平
No. No. We're not gonna do that, y'know why? Because its not an even trade.
好吧  听着
All right, look.
要是你们能保住公寓  又拿到球票呢
What if you could keep the apartment and the tickets?
成交
Done!
让我说完  我是说我们来打赌  赢家才行
Let me finish. I'm talking about a bet. Winner takes all.
我们可能输光
Ooh, we could get nothing.
也可能满载而归  我喜欢
Or you can end up with everything. Oh, I like that.
怎么样
What do you say?
不要  赌了啦
No! Just do it!
真有说服力啊
Oh! Oh, I'm convinced!
拜托啦  我也会为你这么做
Come on, man! You know I'd do it for you.
因为你是我最好的朋友
Because you're my best friend.
好吧  但你一整年不准再用这招
All right. But you can't use that again for a whole year.
我赌了
I'm in.
好兴奋喔  你们要赌什么
This is so exciting! What are you going to bet?
好吧  我们让菲比决定
Okay. Well, we should let Phoebe decide...
因为只有她没有利害关系  而且她好美
...because she's the only one who's impartial, and she's so pretty.
好啊  好啊
Okay. Ha, ha. Um...
太好了  我知道了
Ooh, ooh. Oh, I have a game!
很棒喔  比什么  比什么
This is great! Okay. What's the game? What's the game?
没有名字  要不  叫菲比球
Um, well, it doesn't have a name. No, okay. Phoebe Ball!
不  它没有名字
No, it doesn't have a name. Um...
好  摩妮卡
Okay, Monica.
你最喜欢树的哪一点
What is your favorite thing about trees?
树是绿色的  很好  5分
They're green? Good! Good, five points!
乔伊
All right, Joey...
同样的问题
Same question.
树很高 3分
Oh! Heh. They're tall. Ooh, three points.
都答得很好  但我们说的是阔叶植物  阔叶
Both fine answers, but we were looking for leafy. Leafy.
这根本不是比赛
That's not even a game.
闭嘴  我们领先
Shut up. We're winning!
你们想速战速决  我们就抽牌
You want to finish this? We get a deck of cards.
点数大的赢  如何
High card wins. What do you say?
就这么办   我刚好有牌
Let's do it! Oh, I have cards!
在这里
Oh, good. Yeah. Here.
这是魔术牌
No, these are the trick deck.
那这一副
Okay. Here, yes.
好  你们先抽
Okay, you guys, uh, you pick first.
好的  好的
Okay. Okay?
4点  够小了
Four. That's a low one!
菲比  你看  我不敢看
Phoebe, you look. I can't do it.
为什么我就敢看  好吧
What makes you think I can? That's okay.
1点
你们在爽什么
Why are you screaming and hugging?
因为我们赢回了我们的公寓
Because we won our apartment back!
什么  王牌最大  杰克  皮蛋  老K  王牌
What? Ace is high! Jack, queen, king, ace!
不对  1点最小  1234
No! Ace is low! Ace, two, three, four!
我不知道
I don't know.
你们看
Look it! Aah!
好吧  再抽一次  给我
All right, come on, pick again! Okay.
好  好
Okay. Okay.
来吧  公寓  来吧  公寓
Come on, apartment! Come on, apartment!
皮蛋点数很大
Aah! I know queen is high!
但是大不过
Not as high as...
成功了  老K
It worked! King!
再抽一次  再抽一次
We pick again! We pick again!
为什么  我不知道
Why? I don't know.
球票请拿来
Tickets, please. Ugh!
场边区喔  乖乖
That's courtside, baby! Yeah, ha, ha.
很精彩的比赛  好精彩
Seriously, good game, though. Good game.
她们气什么气  公寓都还给她们了
What are they so mad about? They got the apartment back.
才没有呢
No, they didn't.
嘿
Hey.
趁你不在我打包好了
Packed while you were gone.
我在枕头底下留了一些短裤
I left some knickers under your pillow.
搬来跟我住
Move in with me.
什么
What?
别怕  我知道听起来很疯狂  别人会说太快了
Don't be scared. I-I know it sounds crazy and-and people will say it's too soon,...
但是你想想  那样多棒啊
...but just think. Think how great it would be.
我不知道
I don't know.
要我离开伦敦
Uh, oh, leaving London.
我的家人都在那里  我知道
My whole family lives there... I know.
我的工作  你可以在这里找工作
My job. You'll get a job here.
我常听说美国人的工作  都被外国人抢走了
I mean, I'm always hearing about uh, them foreigners coming in here and stealing American jobs;
你也可以
That could be you.
但事关我的人生
Yeah, but it's my whole life.
你来英国
You come to England.
我不行  我很愿意  但我儿子在这里
I can't. I would. I really would. But my son is here.
我离不开他  没别的办法了吗
I can't leave him. Isn't—you don't think there's any way?
我看是没有了
Oh, I don't think so.
如果是长久的打算就不同了
I mean it would be different if it was way into the future...
例如结婚或什么的
...and we were getting married or something.
什么
What?
喔  好  我不该提 "结婚" 的
Uh, no, right. I shouldn't have said "married."
别被我吓到
Uh, please don't go freaky on me.
我不是认真的  我没说  我收回
I didn't mean it. I didn't say it. I take it back.
不  不要收回
No. Don't.
何不就这么做
Why don't we?
做什么
Why don't we what?
结婚啊
Get married.
你疯了
You are mad!
我没有  这样很完美  比你搬来住更棒
No, I'm not! It's perfect. It's better than you moving here.
我们可以永远在一起  我就是要这样
It's us together forever, and that's what I want.
我们才认识六个星期  我知道
We've known each other six weeks! Yeah, I know.
那又怎样  谁说不行  这样就不行吗
So what? Who's to say? Does that mean we can't do it?
听着  我跟卡萝结婚前  在一起四年
Look. I was with Carol for four years before we got married...
结果是跟一个怀孕的女同志离婚
...and I wound up divorced from a pregnant lesbian.
这么做
I mean, this...
对我们是顺理成章
This makes sense for us.
我们第一次约会  就跑去佛蒙特度周末
Come on. Our first date, we ended up spending the whole weekend in Vermont.
昨晚我还去穿耳洞  是我啊
I mean, last night I got my ear pierced. Me!
这个感觉很对
This feels right.
不是吗
Doesn't it?
我爸妈会气死
My parents are gonna be really mad.
你答应了吗   你同意了
Is that...? Are you saying "Yes"? Is that "Yes"?
是的
Yes.
是的  是的
Yes! Yes?
我们要结婚了 天哪
We're getting married! Oh, my God!
我们要结婚了  天哪
Yes! Ha, ha. We're getting married!
过来  来啊
Come here, come here.
艾蜜莉  你愿意嫁给我吗
Emily, will you marry me?
愿意
Yes.
有一点小了
Oh, it's a bit small.
该死  我原本想这会很浪漫
Damn! I thought that'd be romantic as hell.
是很浪漫
It was.
真是史上最棒的位子
Those were, like, the best seats ever. Oh, yeah.
要不要把衣服送给女生  表示和解
Hey, should we give these to the girls? Like a peace offering?
好主意  反正不用钱又太小
Oh yeah, that's very nice. Plus, y'know they were free and too small.
天哪
Oh, God.
你要喝酒吗
Hey, you want a beer?
我知道
Whoa! I know!
开门  开门  开门
Open up! Open up! Open up!
明天早上再说
We'll discuss it in the morning.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
我们把我们家抢回来了
We took our apartment back!
跟我无关
I had nothing to do with it.
好吧  是我的主意  但我并不好过
Okay, it was my idea. But I don't feel good about it.
我们现在就换回来
We are switching back right now.
不  不要  我们不走
No, we're not. We're not leaving!
你们非走不可  你们都有工作
You'll have to. You both have jobs.
等你们去上班  我们就换回来  你们阻止不了的
As soon as you do, we're switching back! There's nothing you can do to stop us.
对吧  乔伊
Right, Joe?
我不晓得
I don't know.
什么
What?
我不想再搬了
I don't want to move again, with...
我不管  这是我们的公寓  她们偷了
I don't care! This is our apartment and they stole...
你们偷了
You stole!
我们的公寓  我们光明正大的赢了两次
Our apartment! We won it fair and square. Twice!
我现在就要要回来  我现在就要要回来
And I am getting it back right now! I'm getting it back right now!
好
All right.
我们早料到会有这种反应  所以我们准备了备案
We figured you might respond this way, so we have a backup offer.
不要  你们搞不定我们的
Oh, no more offers. You can't offer anything to us!
让我们留在这里  为了表示感谢
Let us keep the apartment and... As a thank you...
瑞秋和我会接吻一分钟
...Rachel and I will kiss for one minute.
完全值得  好爽的一分钟
Totally worth it. That was one good minute.
晚安  晚安
Good night. Good night.
男人真是白痴  就是啊
Men are such idiots. I know.
那么白痴的事  居然让我们得逞了
Can you believe something that stupid actually got us our apartment back?
要是上次比赛完你们就这么做
That's so funny to think if you'd just done that right after the last contest,...
谁都不必搬家了
...no one would have had to move at all. Ha, ha.
就装做没这回事
Let's pretend that's not true. Yeah.
围巾织好了
Okay. Scarf's done.
快点  快点  快点  好
Come on. Come on, come on! Okay.
嘿   嘿
Hey! Hey.
怎么了
What's going on?
罗斯有大事要宣布
Ross has some big thing to tell everyone.
好吧  是
Well, okay. It's, uh... Ahem.
艾蜜莉和我决定
Emily and I, we decided to, uh...
要结婚
...to get married.
什么  天啊
What? Oh, my God.
你也怀孕了
Oh, are you pregnant too?
没有
No.
什么时候  怎么个情况
When did...? How did you...?
我们就是决定要结婚
We just decided to go for it.
这个决定是仓促了些  但是
We know it's a bit hasty, but, uh...
感觉真的很对
...it just feels so right.
我正在告诉他们
Um, I was just telling the guys...
我听到了
Yeah, I heard.
太好了
I think it's great! Aah!
我真替你高兴
I'm so happy for you!
是啊  恭喜
Well, yeah! Congratulations!
你居然要结婚了  是啊
I can't believe you're getting married! Yeah.
摩妮卡和瑞秋亲热
Monica and Rachel made out.
美…好…的…
Morning's here
早晨又来到
The morning's here
阳光露脸
Sunshine is here
晴空万里
The sky is clear
美好的早晨
The morning's here
你回来了
Hey, you're back! Hey!
准备就绪  早餐就快上桌
Get into gear Breakfast is near
夜晚的黑暗一扫而空
The dark of night has disappeared
我们明天见  好
I'll see you tomorrow morning! Okay!